<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HealthCare</string>
    <string name="text1">French Bulldog Temperament: What\'s Good About \'Em, What\'s Bad About \'Em</string>
    <string name="text2">Despite his glum expression, the French Bulldog is comical, entertaining, and dependably amiable.\n\nAs comfortable in an apartment as he is on a farm, he is more lively than you might suspect from his chunky appearance. French Bulldog puppies are especially frisky, and ball chasing is one of their passions. Adults are more dignified and can be champion couch potatoes, but also love to clown around and go for walks in cool weather.\n\nMany Frenchies are friendly with everyone, while others are politely reserved. French Bulldogs will bark to announce visitors, but are otherwise quiet dogs.\n\nUsually peaceful with other pets (though some French Bulldogs will hunt small rodents), males may bicker with other males.\n\nThe French Bulldog is quite stubborn and can be challenging to train, yet also surprisingly sensitive, remembers what he learns, and responds well to early, patient, persistent training that utilizes food motivation.\n\nSnorting, snuffling, and flatulence go with the territory of short-faced breeds.\n\nSwimming pool owners must exercise caution: Because of his squat build and heavy head, most Frenchies cannot swim and will drown if they fall into a pool.</string>
    <string name="text3">If you want a dog who…</string>
    <string name="text4">Is smallish but very sturdy — not a delicate lapdog\n\nHas large expressive eyes\n\nHas a sleek easy-care coat that comes in many colors\n\nIs usually polite with everyone, including other pets\n\nTypically loves to play games and chase balls\n\nDoesn\'t need much exercise\n\nDoesn\'t bark much</string>
    <string name="text5">A French Bulldog may be right for you.</string>
    <string name="text6">If you don\'t want to deal with…</string>
    <string name="text7">Snorting, snuffling, wheezing, snoring, some slobbering\n\nGassiness (flatulence)\n\nStubbornness\n\nSlowness to housebreak\n\nQuite a few potential health problems due to his deformed face\n\nHigh cost</string>
    <string name="text8">A French Bulldog may not be right for you.</string>
    <string name="dog">dog</string>
    <string name="text9">Keep in mind that the inheritance of temperament is less predictable than the inheritance of physical traits such as size or shedding. Temperament and behavior are also shaped by raising and training.</string>
    <string name="text10">You can avoid some negative traits by choosing an ADULT dog from an animal shelter or rescue group. With an adult dog, you can easily see what you\'re getting, and plenty of adult French Bulldogs have already proven themselves not to have negative characteristics.\n\nIf you want a puppy, you can avoid some negative traits by choosing the right breeder and the right puppy. Unfortunately, you usually can\'t tell whether a puppy has inherited temperament or health problems until he grows up.</string>
    <string name="text11">More traits and characteristics of the French Bulldog</string>
    <string name="text12">If I was considering a French Bulldog, I would be most concerned about…\n\n1. Health problems. Unfortunately, these nice-tempered dogs are deliberately bred with structural deformities that detract from the dog\'s quality of life. They especially have trouble breathing. You need to protect them from heatstroke and if your summers get hot, your home needs to be air-conditioned. Along with respiratory disorders, Frenchies also suffer from spinal disorders, eye diseases, heart disease, and joint diseases. Read more about French Bulldog Health.\n\n2. French Bulldog sounds. Because of their short face, most Frenchies snort, snuffle, wheeze, grunt, and snore loudly. These sounds are endearing to some people; nerve-wracking to others.\n\n3. Slobbering. Some French Bulldogs, especially those with heavy loose lips, slobber water when they drink. Some drool, too, especially after eating and drinking.\n\n4. Gassiness (flatulence). All short-faced breeds gulp air when they eat, and that air has to go somewhere, after all!\n\n5. Stubbornness. For such a small dog, French Bulldogs can be quite stubborn and manipulative. You must show them, through absolute consistency, that you mean what you say. Food is a great motivator for this breed, but it often results in a fat Frenchie who only obeys if you\'re waving a cookie. I recommend a more sensible training method.\n\n6. Housebreaking. French Bulldogs can be quite slow to housebreak. Expect four to six months of consistent crate training.</string>
    <string name="save_touch">To Save, Touch Here</string>
    <string name="te1">Training French Bulldogs</string>
    <string name="text13">Dog Training – What Works, And What Doesn\'t</string>
    <string name="text14">Treats can be great motivators. But if your dog will only obey for a treat, then HE is in charge of his obedience, not you.</string>
    <string name="text15">Many dog training methods are based on what makes the OWNER feel good, rather than on what actually makes sense to the DOG. For example…
\n\n"Positive only" dog training has become popular nowadays.
\n\nWith "positive only" dog training, you bribe your dog to do something with food or a toy. If he does the desired behavior, he receives the reward.
\n\n"Positive only" dog training often includes a clicker device – a little metal tab that makes a clicking sound when pressed with your thumb. Clicker training is a form of "conditioning." You click at the precise instant your dog is doing some desired behavior, then immediately give a treat. The dog learns that whenever he hears the clicking sound, whatever behavior he was doing at that instant will bring him food.</string>
    <string name="text16">The problem with "positive only" dog training</string>
    <string name="text17">Positive-only dog training and clicker training work well for teaching fun things – like tricks – where it really doesn\'t matter whether your dog obeys or not. If you tell him to shake hands or roll over and he doesn\'t do it, who cares? But for teaching your dog to come when called in the presence of temptations or distractions.... for teaching your dog to stand quietly while his teeth are brushed or his coat is groomed.... for teaching your dog to act politely toward strangers and other animals....</string>
    <string name="text19">....and for teaching your dog all the other behaviors you want a well-behaved family dog to do (or not do!).... positive-only dog training is less effective.</string>
    <string name="text20">Think about it. What happens when you want your dog to stop chasing a cat and come to you – but at that particular moment he\'s not hungry and would rather chase the cat rather than munch on a biscuit?</string>
    <string name="t1">Owners who rely on positive-only dog training are stuck whenever their dog "isn't in the mood" to do something.</string>
    <string name="t2">An old trainer once said that if a dog really wants to chase a cat, he will chase it "regardless of biscuits showering upon him like manna from heaven."</string>
    <string name="t3">Positive-only dog training does not teach your dog to respect you. And it is RESPECT that motivates a dog to be well-behaved even at times when he doesn\'t feel like it.</string>
    <string name="t4">Why Respect Training makes more sense to dogs</string>
    <string name="t5">Respect Training is a balanced philosophy of dog training. "Balanced" means both positive and negative consequences for one\'s behaviors.</string>
    <string name="t6">Real life for all living creatures consists of learning from both positive and negative consequences.</string>
    <string name="t7">Positive consequences encourage us to repeat a behavior.\n\nNegative consequences discourage us from repeating a behavior.</string>
    <string name="t8">For example, we hold the door open and someone says, "Thank you!" (positive), so we are likely to do it again. We take an extra-long lunch break and the boss docks our pay (negative), so we are less likely to do that again. We learn from both positive and negative consequences and behave accordingly.</string>
    <string name="t9">Your dog learns from both positive and negative consequences. Momma Dog will let Puppy know if he is playing reasonably or if he gets too rough.</string>
    <string name="t10">So do dogs. When a puppy plays with his mother, if his style of play is reasonable, she responds in a positive manner. But if he gets too rough, she is quick to correct with a growl.\n\nDoes Puppy become depressed and never play with another dog again? Of course not. He is happy to play – only more gently.\n\nDogs learn best from balanced dog training, where their behaviors can result in positive OR negative consequences.\n\n - Positive consequences means you reward desirable behaviors with praise, smiles, petting, games, and yes, treats.\n\n - Negative consequences means you correct undesirable behaviors with your voice, your facial expression, your body language, your hands, or with the leash or collar. Now I don\'t mean hitting, yelling, choke collars, or shock collars. I can show you how to correct your dog without being harsh or hurtful.</string>
    <string name="t11">Be realistic and fair with your dog. Show him positive and negative consequences so he can make an informed choice.</string>
    <string name="t12">By showing your dog both positive and negative consequences, he can make a conscious choice to do a behavior (or stop doing a behavior) – not only when he\'s in the mood for a reward/treat, but also when he might not care a hoot about the reward/treat but he still controls himself because he doesn\'t want a correction.
\n\nAll of life works this way – "cause and effect."
\n\nAnd here\'s the best part....</string>
    <string name="t13">When YOU become the arbiter of your dog\'s behaviors – the one who gets to say yea or nay about what he\'s allowed to do – your dog feels respectful toward you.</string>
    <string name="t14">And once your dog respects you, he will listen to you. He will pay attention to you. He will do whatever you ask, and stop any misbehavior upon a single word from you.\n\nYou might like my article on Respect Training.\n\nOr just follow the complete, step-by-step Respect Training program(this app)</string>
    <string name="t18">Meet Kathy Armstrong and Jake</string>
    <string name="t15">Frustrated dog owners often call or email me when their dog has behavior problems and needs training. Here is "Kathy" calling about "Jake."</string>
    <string name="t16">I often get phone calls from distressed owners who are having trouble with their dog.
\n\nLet\'s listen in on a phone conversation between myself and a typical dog owner.... let\'s call her Kathy Armstrong.
\n\nKathy: "Michele, my dog Jake is being difficult! I can't make him do anything. He only listens to me when he's in the mood."
\n\nMe: "I see. Would you say Jake is behaving rudely?"
\n\nKathy (surprised): "What do you mean? How can a dog be rude?"</string>


</resources>
