<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HealthCare</string>
    <string name="text1">French Bulldog Temperament: What\'s Good About \'Em, What\'s Bad About \'Em</string>
    <string name="text2">Despite his glum expression, the French Bulldog is comical, entertaining, and dependably amiable.\n\nAs comfortable in an apartment as he is on a farm, he is more lively than you might suspect from his chunky appearance. French Bulldog puppies are especially frisky, and ball chasing is one of their passions. Adults are more dignified and can be champion couch potatoes, but also love to clown around and go for walks in cool weather.\n\nMany Frenchies are friendly with everyone, while others are politely reserved. French Bulldogs will bark to announce visitors, but are otherwise quiet dogs.\n\nUsually peaceful with other pets (though some French Bulldogs will hunt small rodents), males may bicker with other males.\n\nThe French Bulldog is quite stubborn and can be challenging to train, yet also surprisingly sensitive, remembers what he learns, and responds well to early, patient, persistent training that utilizes food motivation.\n\nSnorting, snuffling, and flatulence go with the territory of short-faced breeds.\n\nSwimming pool owners must exercise caution: Because of his squat build and heavy head, most Frenchies cannot swim and will drown if they fall into a pool.</string>
    <string name="text3">If you want a dog who…</string>
    <string name="text4">Is smallish but very sturdy — not a delicate lapdog\n\nHas large expressive eyes\n\nHas a sleek easy-care coat that comes in many colors\n\nIs usually polite with everyone, including other pets\n\nTypically loves to play games and chase balls\n\nDoesn\'t need much exercise\n\nDoesn\'t bark much</string>
    <string name="text5">A French Bulldog may be right for you.</string>
    <string name="text6">If you don\'t want to deal with…</string>
    <string name="text7">Snorting, snuffling, wheezing, snoring, some slobbering\n\nGassiness (flatulence)\n\nStubbornness\n\nSlowness to housebreak\n\nQuite a few potential health problems due to his deformed face\n\nHigh cost</string>
    <string name="text8">A French Bulldog may not be right for you.</string>
    <string name="dog">dog</string>
    <string name="text9">Keep in mind that the inheritance of temperament is less predictable than the inheritance of physical traits such as size or shedding. Temperament and behavior are also shaped by raising and training.</string>
    <string name="text10">You can avoid some negative traits by choosing an ADULT dog from an animal shelter or rescue group. With an adult dog, you can easily see what you\'re getting, and plenty of adult French Bulldogs have already proven themselves not to have negative characteristics.\n\nIf you want a puppy, you can avoid some negative traits by choosing the right breeder and the right puppy. Unfortunately, you usually can\'t tell whether a puppy has inherited temperament or health problems until he grows up.</string>
    <string name="text11">More traits and characteristics of the French Bulldog</string>
    <string name="text12">If I was considering a French Bulldog, I would be most concerned about…\n\n1. Health problems. Unfortunately, these nice-tempered dogs are deliberately bred with structural deformities that detract from the dog\'s quality of life. They especially have trouble breathing. You need to protect them from heatstroke and if your summers get hot, your home needs to be air-conditioned. Along with respiratory disorders, Frenchies also suffer from spinal disorders, eye diseases, heart disease, and joint diseases. Read more about French Bulldog Health.\n\n2. French Bulldog sounds. Because of their short face, most Frenchies snort, snuffle, wheeze, grunt, and snore loudly. These sounds are endearing to some people; nerve-wracking to others.\n\n3. Slobbering. Some French Bulldogs, especially those with heavy loose lips, slobber water when they drink. Some drool, too, especially after eating and drinking.\n\n4. Gassiness (flatulence). All short-faced breeds gulp air when they eat, and that air has to go somewhere, after all!\n\n5. Stubbornness. For such a small dog, French Bulldogs can be quite stubborn and manipulative. You must show them, through absolute consistency, that you mean what you say. Food is a great motivator for this breed, but it often results in a fat Frenchie who only obeys if you\'re waving a cookie. I recommend a more sensible training method.\n\n6. Housebreaking. French Bulldogs can be quite slow to housebreak. Expect four to six months of consistent crate training.</string>
</resources>
